socialpow.com 2014-05-30

# Privacy Policy

Welcome to the privacy page of this website. We appreciate that you choose us to buy Social Media Services. Before proceeding to use this website, please read this privacy statement to be aware of how we work here to protect your privacy.

**Use of Credit Card Information**

We only use your credit card in order to process your transaction with us. We only use your name, credit card number, and phone number to complete your transaction. Rest assured that your personal and credit card information won’t be shared, sold, or disclosed to a third party. We use a secured socket layer (SSL) to ensure that payment transactions done here are safe.

**Use of Personal Information**

We use your personal information such as your email, name, phone number, and other personal information for data gathering alone. We use this information so that we’ll know how to improve this website and its contents to serve you best. With us, you can be sure that your personal information will be kept confidential at all times.

**Use of Automatically Collected Data**

This website may collect information which includes your length and time of visit, IP address, browser settings, and operating system for statistical purposes alone. This information is used to help us track traffic on our website including the pages that you commonly browse as the user.

**Use of Cookies**

This website may make use of cookies to allow you to access special pages of this website. However, you may also turn off cookies in your discretion, but take note that it will prohibit you from accessing some pages here.

This website may change or alter some parts of this privacy statement with or without notifications. In order to know of these updates, you’re encouraged to visit us often here. In case, you have questions or inquiries on any parts of this privacy statement, please let us know by contacting us through email or phone today.
